<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amber Nguyen</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Amber Nguyen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Python - Regular Expressions</title>
      <link>/blog/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/python/</guid>
      <description>This is a blog post about python and what I have learned in class. Specifically, I thought that regular expressions were really interesting, and I thought that I would share the examples that we learned here.
Regular expressions (Regex) allows you to extract specific information by searching for a match that defines a pattern. I think this is very useful, and it was also cool to learn about!
Here are some of the common regex symbols and their meanings that we learned:Here is a simple example of regex from my homework assignment:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>0. Introductionhappy2015 &amp;lt;- read.csv(&amp;quot;C:/Users/Amber/Desktop/Website/content/2015.csv&amp;quot;)suicides &amp;lt;- read.csv(&amp;quot;C:/Users/Amber/Desktop/Website/content/Copy of who_suicide_statistics.csv&amp;quot;)library(&amp;quot;dplyr&amp;quot;)## ## Attaching package: &amp;#39;dplyr&amp;#39;## The following objects are masked from &amp;#39;package:stats&amp;#39;:## ## filter, lag## The following objects are masked from &amp;#39;package:base&amp;#39;:## ## intersect, setdiff, setequal, unionlibrary(&amp;quot;tidyr&amp;quot;)library(&amp;quot;tidyverse&amp;quot;)## -- Attaching packages -------------------------------------- tidyverse 1.2.1 --## v ggplot2 3.2.1 v purrr 0.3.3## v tibble 2.1.3 v stringr 1.4.0## v readr 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>Amber Nguyen aqn246IntroductionThe dataset that I am using for this project is called the Weights of College Students Backpacks. It includes 9 total variables with 100 observations, but the main variables I will be working with are BackpackWeight, BodyWeight, Ratio, BackProblems, Sex, and Year. BackpackWeight is a measure of each student’s backpack weight in pounds. BodyWeight is a measure of each student’s body weight in pounds. Ratio is the ratio of backpack weight to body weight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Here are some projects I have been working on:
  Project 1
  Project 2
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>Amber NguyenAmber Nguyen was born in Houston, Texas, and currently attends theUniversity of Texas at Austin. She is a Biology Major, graduating in May 2020, hoping to pursue a career in dentistry. She wishes to make a difference in people’s lives through her dedication to community service and the healthcare field.
Other than the sciences, Amber Nguyen is also interested in the arts. Sheenjoys listening to music, singing, and dancing in her free time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>